A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Projects, SG 1.24 (A98) FA1295
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Program and Policy - Members and Meetings, 1970-1984; 903
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Morgan, J. P., 1976-1977 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Pennzoil, 1974-1975 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Perkin-Elmer, 1980 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Pittston Company, 1974-1975 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Southern Company, 1974 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Union Carbide, 1977 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - U.S. Steel, 1974 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Warner-Lambert, 1974 (Box R3184)
- Program and Policy - Personnel, 1918-1984; 909
  - Personnel, 1970-1984 (Box R3185)
    Restricted - Personnel
  - Personnel - General Supplementary Material, 1971-1974 (Box R3185)
  - Personnel - Reports, 1929; 1950 (Box R3185)
  - Personnel - Manual, 1970 (Box R3185)
  - Personnel - Manual - Supplementary Material, 1947-1982 (Box R3185)
  - Personnel - Savings Plan - Reports, 1958; 1964-1967 (Box R3186)
  - Personnel - Salaries, 1918-1950 (Box R3186)